youngadultmoney.com 2019-12-20

# Terms of Use and Privacy Policy | Young Adult Money

Young Adult Money LLC is very concerned about the privacy of your information. Below is our “Privacy Policy” and “Terms of Use.” Please read these carefully before using our website or any of the products or services we administer.

Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website, then you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement.

Young Adult Money LLC may change this policy from time to time by updating this page. You should check this page from time to time to ensure that you are in agreemnet with any changes.

Last modified: May 28, 2018

**Click here to jump to our advertising disclosure**

## General Disclaimer

All content presented here is purely informational and intended for educational purposes only. The information presented is believed to be up-to-date and factual, but Young Adult Money LLC cannot guarantee its accuracy and it should not be considered a complete analysis of the topics discussed.

All expressions of opinion reflect the judgment of the author as of the publication date and are subject to change. The information contained herein does not contain personalized investment advice, nor should it be construed as legal or tax advice. A professional financial advisor, attorney, and/or tax professional should be consulted regarding your specific financial, legal, and/or tax situation. The information presented here is also not an offer to buy or sell securities, nor a solicitation of any offer to buy or sell the securities mentioned herein. 

Neither Young Adult Money LLC, its employees, nor its members make any representations as to the validity, accuracy, completeness, or suitability of any claims made here. Neither Young Adult Money LLC, its employees, nor its members assume any liability with regard to financial results based on the use of the information provided here. Furthermore, advertisers, commenters, and linked sites are solely responsible for their views and content – which do not necessarily represent the views of Young Adult Money LLC, its employees, or its members.

## Copyright

Content published on this website (digital downloads, images, texts, graphics, logos) is the property of Young Adult Money LLC and protected by international copyright laws. The entire compilation of the content found on this website is the exclusive property of Young Adult Money LLC, with copyright authorship for this compilation by Young Adult Money LLC.

## Privacy Policy

This privacy policy has been compiled to better serve those who are concerned with how their ‘Personally Identifiable Information’ (PII) is being used online. PII, as described in US privacy law and information security, is information that can be used on its own or with other information to identify, contact, or locate a single person, or to identify an individual in context. Please read our privacy policy carefully to get a clear understanding of how we collect, use, protect or otherwise handle your Personally Identifiable Information in accordance with our website.

**What personal information do we collect from the people that visit our blog, website or ancillary products such as a spreadsheet?**

When joining our community, registering on our site, filling out a form, or other action as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your name, email address, phone number, State of Residence or other details to help you with your experience.

**When do we collect information?**

We collect information from you when you register on our site, subscribe to our community, subscribe to a newsletter, or fill out a form or enter information on our site.

**How do we use your information?**

We may use the information we collect from you when you register, make a purchase, sign up for our newsletter, sign up for our online community, respond to a survey or marketing communication, surf the website, or use certain other site features in the following ways:

  * To present our site and its contents to you.

  * To provide you with information about your newsletter subscription.

  * To carry out, evaluate and improve our business (which may include sharing your information with our agents and third-party service providers that perform certain functions or services on our behalf, such as data analytics, developing new features for the Site; analyzing and enhancing the user experience on the Site; assessing the effectiveness of our marketing and advertising; and managing our communications).

  * To notify you about changes to our site.

  * To follow up after correspondence (live chat, email or other inquiries)

  * To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site features.

  * To send periodic emails or other forms of contact regarding orders you have submitted, products/services/events we believe may interest you, periodic newsletters to which you may have subscribed, and information about those newsletters.

  * To provide or refer you to specific products or services that you specifically request from us.

  * In any other way we may describe when you provide the information.

  * For any other purpose with your consent.

You may opt out of email communications from us at any time by clicking the “unsubscribe” button in any email you receive from us. We will not share your email address with any third parties unless you direct us to do so.

If you are a resident of a country in the European Economic Area (EEA), please refer to the section below entitled “Additional Rights of EEA Residents.”

**How do we protect your information?**

We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorized access or disclosure, we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.

**Do we use ‘cookies’?**

Yes. Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computer’s hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the site’s or service provider’s systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information. For instance, we use cookies to help us remember and process the items in your shopping cart. They are also used to help us understand your preferences based on previous or current site activity, which enables us to provide you with improved services. We also use cookies to help us compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future.

**We use cookies to:**

  * Understand and save user’s preferences for future visits.

  * Keep track of and serve advertisements.

  * Compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interactions in order to offer better site experiences and tools in the future. We may also use trusted third-party services that track this information on our behalf.

You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer.

Since each browser is a little different, look at your browser’s Help Menu to learn the correct way to modify your cookies.

**If users disable cookies in their browser:**

If you turn cookies off it will turn off some of the features of the site. This may prevent you from taking full advantage of the website.

**Third-party disclosure**

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your Personally Identifiable Information unless we provide users with advance notice. This does not include website hosting partners and other parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or serving our users, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release information when it’s release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies and terms of use (see below), or protect ours or others’ rights, property or safety.

However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

**Third-party links**

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third-party products or services on our website. These third-party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

**Google**

Google’s advertising requirements can be summed up by Google’s Advertising Principles. They are put in place to provide a positive experience for users. <https://support.google.com/adwordspolicy/answer/1316548?hl=en>

We use Google AdSense Advertising on our website.

Google, as a third-party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on our site. Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to our users based on previous visits to our site and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt-out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google Ad and Content Network privacy policy.

We, along with third-party vendors such as Google use first-party cookies (such as the Google Analytics cookies) and third-party cookies or other third-party identifiers together to compile data regarding user interactions with ad impressions and other ad service functions as they relate to our website.

**Controlling Your Information and Opting out:**

Google is restricted in its ability to use and share information collected by Google Analytics by the Google Analytics Terms of Use and the Google Privacy Policy. Users can set preferences for how Google advertises to you using the Google Ad Settings page. Alternatively, you can opt out by visiting the Network Advertising Initiative Opt Out page or by using the Google Analytics Opt Out Browser add on.

**For European Economic Area Residents**

If you reside in a country in the European Economic Area (EEA), then under the GDPR and applicable data protection laws you have the rights, among other things, to access your personal data, have us erase it, and/or restrict its further processing. 

If you wish to access or delete your personal data (if any) maintained by us related to advertising on the Site, you can contact us at info@YoungAdultMoney.com.

Young Adult Money LLC uses Google Analytics Demographics and Interest Reporting. Visitors can opt-out of Google Analytics for Display Advertising and customize Google Display Network ads using Google’s [Ad Settings page](https://www.google.com/settings/ads). Users can completely block Google Analytics tracking using [Google’s Analytics Opt-out browser add-on](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout/).

**Opting out of Internet Based Advertising (IBA):**

You may control your personal information and advertising choices at [http://optout.aboutads.info](http://optout.aboutads.info/). You may also opt out of receiving IBA from many sites by visiting the Digital Advertising Alliance (“DAA”) at the [DAA consumer choice service](http://www.aboutads.info/) and the Network Advertising Initiative (“NAI”) at the [NAI Service](https://www.networkadvertising.org/). Please note that all tools provided at the [DAA opt-out page](http://optout.aboutads.info/#!/) and the [NAI opt-out page](http://optout.networkadvertising.org/#!/) are provided by third parties, not Adult Money LLC.

**Fair Information Practices**

The Fair Information Practices Principles form the backbone of privacy law in the United States and the concepts they include have played a significant role in the development of data protection laws around the globe. Understanding the Fair Information Practice Principles and how they should be implemented is critical to comply with the various privacy laws that protect personal information.

In order to be in line with Fair Information Practices we will take the following responsive action, should a data breach occur:

We will notify you via email within 7 business days. We will notify the users via in-site notification within 7 business days.

We also agree to the Individual Redress Principle which requires that individuals have the right to legally pursue enforceable rights against data collectors and processors who fail to adhere to the law. This principle requires not only that individuals have enforceable rights against data users, but also that individuals have recourse to courts or government agencies to investigate and/or prosecute non-compliance by data processors.

**COPPA (Children Online Privacy Protection Act)**

When it comes to the collection of personal information from children under the age of 13 years old, the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA) puts parents in control. The Federal Trade Commission, United States’ consumer protection agency, enforces the COPPA Rule, which spells out what operators of websites and online services must do to protect children’s privacy and safety online.

We do not specifically market to children under the age of 13 years old and do not knowingly collect any information from children under 13 years of age on this site. If we learn we have collected or received personal information from a child under 13 without verification of parental consent, we are happy to delete that information. Please contact us at info@YoungAdultMoney.com with concerns.

**CAN SPAM Act**

The CAN-SPAM Act is a law that sets the rules for commercial email, establishes requirements for commercial messages, gives recipients the right to have emails stopped from being sent to them, and spells out tough penalties for violations.

To be in accordance with CANSPAM, we agree to the following:

  * Not use false or misleading subjects or email addresses.

  * Identify the message as an advertisement in some reasonable way.

  * Include the physical address of our business or site headquarters.

  * Monitor third-party email marketing services for compliance, if one is used.

  * Honor opt-out/unsubscribe requests quickly.

  * Allow users to unsubscribe by using the link at the bottom of each email.

**Additional Rights of EEA (European Economic Area) Residents**

If you are a resident of a country in the EEA, you have the rights, among others, to:

  * Access your personal data

  * Ensure the accuracy of your personal data

  * The right to have us delete your personal data

  * The right to restrict further processing of your personal data, and

  * The right to complain to a supervisory authority in your country of residence in the event that data is misused

If you believe that our processing of your personal information infringes data protection laws, you have a legal right to lodge a complaint with a supervisory authority responsible for data protection. You may do so in the EU member state of your residence, your place of work or the place of the alleged infringement.

You may exercise any of your rights in relation to your personal data by written notice to us addressed to the following:

Young Adult Money LLC  
P.O. Box 130713  
St. Paul, MN 55113  
USA  
info@YoungAdultMoney.com

## Advertising Disclosure

Young Adult Money LLC receives compensation from some of the companies that appear on the website. This may affect the order and manner in which they appear. This site does not include or review all companies or available products. Additionally, the views and opinions expressed are purely the author’s own. Unless otherwise noted, editorial content is not provided, reviewed, approved, or otherwise endorsed by the companies mentioned. Read our full disclosure statement here.

Young Adult Money LLC is an independent personal finance website that is owned and operated by Young Adult Money LLC (a limited liability company governed under the State of Minnesota) and supported through advertising.

Per FTC guidelines, this website receives compensation from some of the companies that appear on the website. This may affect the order and manner in which they appear. This site does not include or review all companies or available products. Additionally, the views and opinions expressed are purely the author’s own. Unless otherwise noted, editorial content is not provided, reviewed, approved or otherwise endorsed by any of the companies mentioned.

Any references to third party products, rates, or websites are subject to change without notice. Any product claim, statistic, quote, or other representation about a product or service should be verified with the manufacturer, provider, or party in question.

Young Adult Money LLC is a participant in the Amazon Services LLC Associates Program, an affiliate advertising program designed to provide a means for sites to earn advertising fees by advertising and linking to Amazon.com.

If you have any questions at all about advertising on YoungAdultMoney.com please do not hesitate to [contact us](https://www.youngadultmoney.com/contact/).

## Comments, Reviews, and Emails

Visitors may post content as long as it is not obscene, illegal, defamatory, threatening, infringing of intellectual property rights, invasive of privacy or injurious in any other way to third parties. Content has to be free of software viruses, political campaign, and commercial solicitation.

We reserve all rights (but not the obligation) to remove and/or edit such content. When you post your content, you grant Young Adult Money LLC non-exclusive, royalty-free and irrevocable right to use, reproduce, publish, modify such content throughout the world in any media.

We reserve all rights to terminate accounts, edit or remove content and cancel orders in their sole discretion.

## License and Site Access

We grant you a limited license to access and make personal use of this website. You are not allowed to download or modify it. This may be done only with written consent from us.

## Applicable Law

By visiting this website, you agree that the laws of the State of Minnesota, without regard to principles of conflict laws, will govern these terms of service, or any dispute of any sort that might come between Young Adult Money LLC and you, or its business partners and associates.

## Disputes

Any dispute related in any way to your visit to this website or to products you purchase from us shall be arbitrated by state or federal court in Minnesota and you consent to exclusive jurisdiction and venue of such courts.

## Contacting Us

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy or terms of use, you may contact us using the information below.

Young Adult Money LLC  
P.O. Box 130713  
St. Paul, MN 55113  
USA  
info@YoungAdultMoney.com
